

Profile

Starting as a passionate graphic designer working with small businesses and agencies; I gradually adapted the ability to code and develop my own creative vision into functioning user experiences. Working as a team player to establish foundation for new visions and products has been a dream of mine. Being able to continue on this path of learning has opened my eyes to becoming a Front End Developer.

Employment History

Web Designer, Quips, Tempe

JULY 2020 - AUGUST 2021

This position aimed at expanding the current landscape of a moving company updating itself into a the modern landscape. As the lead web designer I created:

- Brochures, Fliers & Promotion, and needed Print Collateral
- Updated & Expanded UX for a more seamless interaction between company and customer
- Worked on future endeavors such as: API documentation and Investor Pitch Decks
- Established Email, Social Campaigns and Promotions
- Face to Face Customer Service

Quality Assurance Anaylst, Fair, Phoenix

MARCH 2019 - OCTOBER 2020

This position aimed to:

- Identify key pain points in the companies current UX.
- Update outdated teaching materials.
- Rely data to correct departments to inline bodies on company goals and policies
- Analyze and Report on the customers experiences when using the app
- Collect data across multiple channels for review and presentation

Web Designer, Mediphor Design, Tempe

JANUARY 2019 - JANUARY 2020

This position aimed to:

- Update the companies current web presence and showcase new industrial products
- Establish relationships with clients and build websites for their products
- Create pitch decks for investor cycles
- Manage e-comm sales and inventory for house products
- Run and Develop Social media content

Worpress Designer, Endurance International, Tempe

JUNE 2018 - DECEMBER 2019

This position aimed to:

- Build and Manage 10+ client sites a month
- Create WordPress themes for high volume site design
- moderate issues regarding hosting and DNS

Details

Phoenix, 85048 4802290548 Bisraddesign@gmail.com

Links

Design Portfolio

Dev Porfolio

<u>GitHub</u>

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

jQuery

Node.js

React

Graphic Deisgner, Sandoval Agency, Chandler

JANUARY 2017 - JUNE 2018

This position aimed to:

- Create print collateral for clients
- Social media content creation
- Establish agency and community relationships
- Work with high profile clients such as: LionsGate

Education

Associates of Science in Graphic Design, The Art Institute, Phoenix

JANUARY 2014 - MARCH 2016

Create and appraise graphic designs related to graphic design applications, integrated graphics, digital imaging for artists, and web page design and development utilizing various graphic design computer programs such as Adobe Illustrator, PhotoShop, and InDesign.

Courses

Master Gatsby, Wes Bos

NOVEMBER 2020 - JANUARY 2021

React for Beginners, Wes Bos

AUGUST 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

Beginner JavaScript, Wes Bos

SEPTEMBER 2020 - AUGUST 2020

Front End Developement, Treehouse

JULY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Advanced React, Wes Bos

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

References

References available upon request